Unit one. This is me.
Lungs.
Breathe.
What can you do with your lungs?
I can breathe with my lungs.
Hands.
Feet.
What do you use your hands for?
I use my hands for waving.
What do you use your feet for?
I use my feet for running.
Fridge.
Sofa.
Kitchen.
Living room.
Cooker.
TV.
What do you see in the kitchen?
I see food in the fridge.
What do you see in the living room?
I see a cat on the sofa.
Mother.
Father.
What does your father do?
He is a doctor.
What does your mother do?
She is a teacher.
Brush.
Teeth.
Fruits.
Milk.
Vegetables.
Candies.
Cakes.
Chocolate.
What do you do for your teeth?
I brush my teeth.
What foods are good for your teeth?
Fruits, vegetables, and milk.
What foods are not good for your teeth?
Candies, cakes, and chocolate.
Friends.
Take turns.
How do you play with your friends?
I take turns playing with my friends.